(this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz"]=this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz"]||[]).push([[0],{14:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n.p+"static/media/logo.6387c00b.svg"},16:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(50)},21:function(e,t,n){},49:function(e,t,n){},50:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var i=n(0),o=n.n(i),a=n(4),s=n.n(a),r=(n(21),n(1));var l=[{question:'Where was the first "sit-in" at a segregated lunch counter?',answers:[{content:"Greensboro, North Carolina",type:!0},{content:"Jackson, Mississippi",type:!1},{content:"Charleston, South Carolina",type:!1}],postAnswer:"The Greensboro sit-ins were a series of nonviolent protests in February to July 1960, primarily in the Woolworth store, now the International Civil Rights Center and Museum, in Greensboro, North Carolina, which led to the F. W. Woolworth Company department store chain removing its policy of racial segregation in the Southern United States.",wikiLink:"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Greensboro_sit-ins"},{question:"Which Supreme Court case ruled that the segregation of public schools was unconstitutional?",answers:[{content:"Brown v. Board of Education",type:!0},{content:"Plessy v. Ferguson",type:!1},{content:"Dred Scott v. Sandford",type:!1}],postAnswer:'Brown v. Board of Education of Topeka, was a landmark decision of the U.S. Supreme Court in which the Court ruled that U.S. state laws establishing racial segregation in public schools are unconstitutional, even if the segregated schools are otherwise equal in quality. Handed down on May 17, 1954, the Court\'s unanimous (9\u20130) decision stated that "separate educational facilities are inherently unequal," and therefore violate the Equal Protection Clause of the Fourteenth Amendment of the U.S. Constitution. However, the decision\'s 14 pages did not spell out any sort of method for ending racial segregation in schools, and the Court\'s second decision in Brown II in 1955 only ordered states to desegregate "with all deliberate speed."',wikiLink:"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brown_v._Board_of_Education"},{question:"What was the outcome of the murder trial of Emmet Till?",answers:[{content:"The two defends were acquitted by an all white jury",type:!0},{content:"The two defendents were given life in prison",type:!1},{content:"The two defendents were given the death sentence",type:!1}],postAnswer:"In September 1955, an all-white jury found Bryant and Milam not guilty of Till's kidnapping and murder. Protected against double jeopardy, the two men publicly admitted in a 1956 interview with Look magazine that they had killed Till. Till's murder was seen as a catalyst for the next phase of the civil rights movement.",wikiLink:"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Emmett_Till"},{question:"What event was the catalyst for the Montgomery Bus Boycott?",answers:[{content:"Claudette Colvin and Rosa Parks refused to give up their seats to a white person on a public bus",type:!0},{content:"A segregated bus system was established in Montgomery, Alabama",type:!1},{content:"Bus fairs were raised only for Black passengers",type:!1}],postAnswer:'On December 1, 1955, nine months after a 15-year-old high school student, Claudette Colvin, refused to give up her seat to a white passenger on a public bus in Montgomery, Alabama, and was arrested, Rosa Parks did the same thing. Parks soon became the symbol of the resulting Montgomery Bus Boycott and received national publicity. She was later hailed as the "mother of the civil rights movement".',wikiLink:"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Montgomery_Bus_Boycott"},{question:"How did Arkansas Governor Orval Faubus respond to the effort of the nine African Americans to attend Little Rock High School in 1957?",answers:[{content:"He asked the president to intervene and block the school\u2019s integration",type:!0},{content:"He urged the school to treat the students fairly",type:!1},{content:"He called out the National Guard to block their way",type:!1}],postAnswer:"A crisis erupted in Little Rock, Arkansas, when Governor of Arkansas Orval Faubus called out the National Guard on September 4 to prevent entry to the nine African-American students who had sued for the right to attend an integrated school, Little Rock Central High School.[60] Under the guidance of Daisy Bates, the nine students had been chosen to attend Central High because of their excellent grades.",wikiLink:"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Little_Rock_Nine"},{question:"Which Civil Rights organization sent out youth field organizers to lead sit-ins, encourage Black voter registration, and challenge civil segregation?",answers:[{content:"Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee",type:!0},{content:"Fellowship of Reconciliation",type:!1},{content:"Congress of Racial Equality",type:!1}],postAnswer:"The Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee was the principal channel of student commitment in the United States to the Civil Rights Movement during the 1960s. Emerging in 1960 from the student-led sit-ins at segregated lunch counters in Greensboro, North Carolina and Nashville, Tennessee, the Committee sought to coordinate and assist direct-action challenges to the civic segregation and political exclusion of African-Americans.",wikiLink:"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Student_Nonviolent_Coordinating_Committee"},{question:'Which organization challenged the non-enforcement of the Supreme Court\'s ruling that "segregated public buses were unconstitutional?"',answers:[{content:"Freedom Riders",type:!0},{content:"Students for a Democratic Society",type:!1},{content:"Prayer Pilgrimage",type:!1}],postAnswer:"The Freedom Riders were inspired by the 1947 Journey of Reconciliation, led by Bayard Rustin and George Houser and co-sponsored by the Fellowship of Reconciliation and the then-fledgling Congress of Racial Equality (CORE). Like the Freedom Rides of 1961, the Journey of Reconciliation was intended to test an earlier Supreme Court ruling that banned racial discrimination in interstate travel. The first Freedom Ride began on May 4, 1961 and included seven black and six white riders.",wikiLink:"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Freedom_Riders"},{question:"Founded by representatives of SNCC, CORE, and the NAACP in 1962, which organization led an effort to register Black voters throughout Mississippi?",answers:[{content:"Council of Federated Organizations",type:!0},{content:"Voter Education Project",type:!1},{content:"Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party",type:!1}],postAnswer:"The Council of Federated Organizations (COFO) was a coalition of the major Civil Rights Movement organizations operating in Mississippi. COFO was formed in 1961 to coordinate and unite voter registration and other civil rights activities in the state and oversee the distribution of funds from the Voter Education Project. It was instrumental in forming the Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party.",wikiLink:"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Council_of_Federated_Organizations"},{question:"Propelled by their previously lackluster response to the civil rights activism in the early 1960s, the Kennedy administration federally endorsed which organizing effort?",answers:[{content:"The Voter Education Project",type:!0},{content:"The Civil Liberties Project",type:!1},{content:"Voting Rights Act of 1965",type:!1}],postAnswer:"Starting in 1960, the explosion of student-led activism of sit-ins, and Freedom Rides during the Civil Rights Movement created a public relations and foreign policy embarrassment for the Kennedy administration. Voter Education Project (VEP) raised and distributed foundation funds to civil rights organizations for voter education and registration work in the southern United States from 1962 to 1992. The project was federally endorsed by the Kennedy administration in hopes that the organizations of the ongoing Civil Rights Movement would shift their focus away from demonstrations and more towards the support of voter registration.",wikiLink:"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Voter_Education_Project"},{question:"After applying and being rejected from Mississippi Southern College, this Black Korean War-veteran published a series of letters about the need for desegregation and was imprisoned by the state of Mississippi on false charges",answers:[{content:"Clyde Kennard",type:!0},{content:"Dick Gregory",type:!1},{content:"Medgar Evers",type:!1}],postAnswer:"In the 1950s, Clyde Kennard attempted several times to enroll at the all-white Mississippi Southern College (now the University of Southern Mississippi) to complete his undergraduate degree started at the University of Chicago. Although the United States Supreme Court had ruled in 1954 that segregation of public schools was unconstitutional, USM rejected him. After Kennard published a letter in the local paper about integrated education, the Mississippi State Sovereignty Commission, a state-supported agency, conspired to have him arrested on false charges.",wikiLink:"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Clyde_Kennard"},{question:"Which coalition was active in Southwest Georgia and sought to draw attention to brutally enforced racial segregation practices in the area?",answers:[{content:"Albany Movement",type:!0},{content:"Georgia Coalition",type:!1},{content:"Criterion Club",type:!1}],postAnswer:"The Albany Movement was a desegregation and voters' rights coalition formed in Albany, Georgia, in November 1961. This movement was founded by local black leaders and ministers, as well as members of the Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC) and the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP). This group has been assisted by Martin Luther King Jr. and the Southern Christian Leadership Conference(SCLS).",wikiLink:"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Albany_Movement"},{question:"Built off of lessons learned during the Albany Movement, this effort garnered international attention and served as a model of nonviolent direct action protest",answers:[{content:"Birmingham Campaign",type:!0},{content:"Southern Protest Movement",type:!1},{content:"Mississippi Movement",type:!1}],postAnswer:"The Birmingham campaign, or Birmingham movement, was a movement organized in early 1963 by the Southern Christian Leadership Conference (SCLC) to bring attention to the integration efforts of African Americans in Birmingham, Alabama. Led by Martin Luther King Jr., James Bevel, Fred Shuttlesworth and others, the campaign of nonviolent direct action culminated in widely publicized confrontations between young black students and white civic authorities, and eventually led the municipal government to change the city's discrimination laws.",wikiLink:"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Birmingham_campaign"},{question:"The brainchild of SCLC officer James Bevel, this bold and controversial strategy used during the Birmingham Campaign led to direct intervention by JFK.",answers:[{content:"Children's Crusade",type:!0},{content:"Letter from Birmingham Jail",type:!1},{content:"Lunch Counter Sit-ins",type:!1}],postAnswer:"In what would be called the Children's Crusade, more than one thousand students skipped school on May 2 to meet at the 16th Street Baptist Church in Birmingham to join the demonstrations. More than six hundred marched out of the church fifty at a time in an attempt to walk to City Hall to speak to Birmingham's mayor about segregation. They were arrested and put into jail. On the next day, however, another one thousand students gathered at the church. When Bevel started them marching fifty at a time, Bull Connor finally unleashed police dogs on them and then turned the city's fire hoses water streams on the children. National television networks broadcast the scenes and widespread public outrage led the Kennedy administration to intervene more forcefully in negotiations between the white business community and the SCLC.",wikiLink:"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Children%27s_Crusade"},{question:'During which organized march did Martin Luther King recite his historic "I Have a Dream" speech?',answers:[{content:"March on Washington for Jobs and Freedom",type:!0},{content:"Selma to Montgomery Marches",type:!1},{content:"Bloody Sunday",type:!1}],postAnswer:'The March on Washington for Jobs and Freedom was held in Washington, D.C. on Wednesday, August 28, 1963. The purpose of the march was to advocate for the civil and economic rights of African Americans. At the march, Martin Luther King Jr., standing in front of the Lincoln Memorial, delivered his historic "I Have a Dream" speech in which he called for an end to racism. The march was organized by A. Philip Randolph and Bayard Rustin, who built an alliance of civil rights, labor, and religious organizations.',wikiLink:"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/March_on_Washington_for_Jobs_and_Freedom"},{question:"Which 1965 effort, launched in the wake of the murder of Jimmie Lee Jackson, led to the passage of the Voting Rights Act?",answers:[{content:"Selma to Montgomery Marches",type:!0},{content:"Alabama Voting Rights Project",type:!1},{content:"Northern Campaign",type:!1}],postAnswer:"The Selma to Montgomery marches were three protest marches, held in 1965, along the 54-mile (87 km) highway from Selma, Alabama, to the state capital of Montgomery. The marches were organized by nonviolent activists to demonstrate the desire of African-American citizens to exercise their constitutional right to vote, in defiance of segregationist repression; they were part of a broader voting rights movement underway in Selma and throughout the American South. By highlighting racial injustice, stemming from the murder of activist and deacon Jimmie Lee Jackson  by state trooper James Bonard Fowler, they contributed to passage that year of the Voting Rights Act, a landmark federal achievement of the civil rights movement.",wikiLink:"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Selma_to_Montgomery_marches"}],h=n(5);var c=function(e){return o.a.createElement("h2",{className:"question"},e.content)};var d=function(e){return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"questionCount"})},u=n(15),m=n(13),p=n.n(m);var w=function(e){const t=Object(i.useState)(!1),n=Object(u.a)(t,2),a=n[0],s=n[1],r=e.answered&&e.isTrue?{background:"rgb(75, 181, 67)",color:"white"}:a?{background:"#B33A3A",color:"white"}:{};return o.a.createElement("li",{className:"answerOption",style:r},o.a.createElement("input",{type:"radio",className:"radioCustomButton",name:"radioGroup",checked:e.answer&&e.isTrue,id:e.answerType,value:e.answerType,disabled:e.answer,onChange:t=>{e.isTrue||s(!0),e.onAnswerSelected(e.isTrue,e.postAnswer,e.wikiLink,t)}}),o.a.createElement(p.a,{isOpen:e.answer&&e.isTrue&&!1,preferPlace:"left",body:[o.a.createElement("div",{style:{background:"white",width:"fit-content",padding:"2px",borderRadius:"20px"}},o.a.createElement("a",{key:"a",onClick:e.openLearnMore,className:"link"},"read more")),o.a.createElement("div",{key:"b",style:{width:"500px",padding:"10px",borderRadius:"20px",background:"rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.7)",color:"black"}},o.a.createElement("span",{style:{lineHeight:1.8,background:"white"}},e.postAnswer))]},o.a.createElement("label",{className:"radioCustomLabel",htmlFor:e.answerType},e.answerContent)))};var g=function(e){return o.a.createElement(h.CSSTransitionGroup,{className:"container",component:"div",transitionName:"fade",transitionEnterTimeout:400,transitionLeaveTimeout:100,transitionAppear:!0,transitionAppearTimeout:500},o.a.createElement("div",{key:e.questionId},o.a.createElement(d,{counter:e.questionId,total:e.questionTotal}),o.a.createElement(c,{content:e.question}),o.a.createElement("ul",{className:"answerOptions"},e.answerOptions.map((function(t){return o.a.createElement(w,{key:t.content,answerContent:t.content,answerType:t.content,isTrue:t.type,postAnswer:e.postAnswer,answered:""!=e.learnMoreLink,wikiLink:e.wikiLink,answer:e.answer,questionId:e.questionId,onAnswerSelected:e.onAnswerSelected,openLearnMore:e.openLearnMore})}))),""!==e.learnMoreLink&&o.a.createElement("div",{className:"quizzBox",style:{background:e.rightAnswer?"#4bb543":"#B33A3A"}},o.a.createElement(d,{counter:e.questionId,total:e.questionTotal}),o.a.createElement(c,{content:e.question}),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"answerExplanationContainer"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"answerExplanation"},e.postAnswer),o.a.createElement("a",{key:"a",className:"learnMoreLink",style:{color:"white"},onClick:e.openLearnMore},"Learn more")))))};var f=function(e){return o.a.createElement(h.CSSTransitionGroup,{className:"container result",component:"div",transitionName:"fade",transitionEnterTimeout:800,transitionLeaveTimeout:500,transitionAppear:!0,transitionAppearTimeout:500},o.a.createElement("div",null,"Completed!"))},y=n(14),k=n.n(y);n(49);class v extends o.a.Component{constructor(e){super(e)}render(){const e=this.props,t=e.ref,n=e.url;return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"wikiContainer",ref:t},o.a.createElement("iframe",{className:"wikiIframe",title:"wiki-iframe",src:n}))}}var b=v;class C extends i.Component{constructor(e){super(e),this.state={counter:0,nextButton:!1,questionId:1,question:"",answerOptions:[],answer:"",answersCount:{},result:"",wikiLink:"",activeWikiLink:"",learnMoreContent:"",learnMoreLink:"",validAnswers:0,questionsAnswered:0,rightAnswer:!1},this.wikiEl=o.a.createRef(),this.setNextQuestion=this.setNextQuestion.bind(this),this.handleAnswerSelected=this.handleAnswerSelected.bind(this),this.openLearnMore=this.openLearnMore.bind(this)}componentDidMount(){const e=l.map(e=>this.shuffleArray(e.answers));this.setState({question:l[0].question,postAnswer:l[0].postAnswer,wikiLink:l[0].wikiLink,answerOptions:e[0]})}shuffleArray(e){for(var t,n,i=e.length;0!==i;)n=Math.floor(Math.random()*i),t=e[i-=1],e[i]=e[n],e[n]=t;return e}handleAnswerSelected(e,t,n,i){this.setUserAnswer(i.currentTarget.value);const o=this.state.validAnswers,a=e?Number(o+1):o;this.setState(Object(r.a)(Object(r.a)({},this.state),{},{learnMoreContent:t,learnMoreLink:n,rightAnswer:e,validAnswers:a,questionsAnswered:this.state.questionsAnswered+1})),this.state.questionId<l.length?this.setState({nextButton:!0}):setTimeout(()=>this.setResults(this.getResults()),8e3)}setUserAnswer(e){this.setState((t,n)=>({answersCount:Object(r.a)(Object(r.a)({},t.answersCount),{},{[e]:(t.answersCount[e]||0)+1}),answer:e}))}setNextQuestion(){const e=this.state.counter+1,t=this.state.questionId+1;this.setState({counter:e,questionId:t,nextButton:!1,question:l[e].question,answerOptions:l[e].answers,postAnswer:l[e].postAnswer,wikiLink:l[e].wikiLink,answer:"",learnMoreContent:"",learnMoreLink:""})}openLearnMore(){this.setState(Object(r.a)(Object(r.a)({},this.state),{},{activeWikiLink:this.state.wikiLink})),console.log(this.wikiEl.current),window.setTimeout(()=>{this.wikiEl.current.scrollIntoView({alignToTop:!0,behavior:"smooth"})},100)}getResults(){const e=this.state.answersCount,t=Object.keys(e),n=t.map(t=>e[t]),i=Math.max.apply(null,n);return t.filter(t=>e[t]===i)}setResults(e){this.setState({result:"completed"})}renderQuiz(){return o.a.createElement(o.a.Fragment,null,o.a.createElement(g,{answer:this.state.answer,answerOptions:this.state.answerOptions,questionId:this.state.questionId,question:this.state.question,postAnswer:this.state.postAnswer,wikiLink:this.state.wikiLink,questionTotal:l.length,onAnswerSelected:this.handleAnswerSelected,openLearnMore:this.openLearnMore,learnMoreContent:this.state.learnMoreContent,learnMoreLink:this.state.learnMoreLink,rightAnswer:this.state.rightAnswer}),this.state.nextButton?o.a.createElement("button",{onClick:this.setNextQuestion,className:"next-button"},"NEXT"):null,this.state.questionsAnswered>0&&o.a.createElement("div",{className:"validAnswersContainer"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"title"})))}renderResult(){return o.a.createElement(f,{quizResult:this.state.result})}render(){return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"App-header"},o.a.createElement("img",{src:k.a,className:"App-logo",alt:"logo"}),o.a.createElement("h2",null,"Civil Rights Quizz")),this.state.result?this.renderResult():this.renderQuiz(),o.a.createElement("div",{ref:this.wikiEl},this.state.activeWikiLink&&o.a.createElement(b,{url:this.state.activeWikiLink})))}}var A=C;Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));s.a.render(o.a.createElement(A,null),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then(e=>{e.unregister()})}},[[16,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.e42e30cd.chunk.js.map